{
    "id": "df8f2f240bbd4a9190b6f30e3d8b20a8",
    "title": "If And Unless Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will take the job ………………… the pay is too low.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0395bc193bdf4245bb17661a26b40536"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be back tomorrow ………………….. there is a plane strike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "831e0e8e65f34d5ab876861b34d26f9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go for a walk – …………………  you are too tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a083ecf649134c8f8777eea96c2476d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to work in the garden this afternoon, …………………. it rains.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "142b0950677340179561beed82f2300e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be surprised ………………….. he doesn’t have an accident soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d2eae069a4d4d2b8a66abcbe1b11828"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think she would look prettier …………………. she didn’t wear so much make-up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bad251d0d79b4da7a51f84589d96c222"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you don’t stop smoking, you will fall seriously ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8df62e575cde4a45af70cef750c5bb17"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you start now, you will not reach there in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fca95e2fd2614a1bb756345bfb9f20ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. I were rich, I would spend all my time traveling.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acbd61b2b4124d0ca22c813e85e4a821"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. I have enough time tomorrow, I will come and see you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "745178d4df0a4eb7b6fd72189cdce66a"
        }
    ]
}